## Munseong Jeong (Leon)

FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### **Profile**

I am a front-end programmer and designer with 5 years and familiar with HTML, CSS, JavaScript also experienced with numerous programming languages/tools including React, Typescript, NodeJs, MySQL, Git. I enjoy learning new languages and development techniques. Based on design experience I am good to use of Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma and AdobeXD tools and analyzing tools like Tableau and Power Bi. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. My career goal is become a full-stack developer.

## **Employment History**

# FrontEnd Developer (volunteer project), Trans Tasman Energy Group, Melbourne

MAY 2022 - PRESENT

TTEG is providing solutions of energy requirements for the large, small and medium businesses. Which using self developed customer management system.

My responsibilities were:

- Created Retailer, Company, Council and Association list and detail pages.
- Fetch the data from API then filter or sort them.
- Technologies used: React, Typescript, Material UI, Git, Bitbucket,
- Agile mode develop environment
- Deploy the website to the server.
- Use design tool to create the layout of the website.
- Communicated with customers to discuss their needs.

#### Analyst Programmer, EASI Australia Pty Ltd , Melbourne

OCTOBER 2019 - MARCH 2022

EASI Australia is a well-known international food delivery corporation.

My responsibilities were:

- Creating and maintaining websites, including desktop and mobile user interface pages and admin system pages, mainly based on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, W2UI, JSP and Java.
- Test, debug and fix errors of Web accessibility (HTML, CSS).
- Test, debug, diagnose and correct errors in users' strategic reporting and analytical functions.
- Develop and design strategic reporting and analytical functions to meet business requirements (SQL, Tableau).
- Provide advice in developing strategic reporting and analytical functions.
- Use Tableau to analyze data, generate visualization data, and allocate human resources according to the data.
- Take data from databases, mainly based on MySQL.
- Integrate data from various back-end services, systems, and databases.
- Maintaining UI design of the admin system and mobile app, mainly creating ad banners, posters and renewing layout of the app. Amend diversity food pictures, restaurant photos and menu (Photoshop).

#### Front-End Web Designer, DamingGlass Pty Ltd, South Korea

#### **Details**

CARLTON, 3000
Australia
0452462858
jmunseng@gmail.com

#### Links

**Portfolio** 

LinkedIn

Github

#### **Skills**

HTML, CSS, Javascript

UI Design, Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, Adobe XD,

React, TypeScript, Material UI, Java, SQL, Oracle, MongoDB

Data Analysis, Power BI, Tableau, Microsoft Office, Effective Time Management

Node.js, JQuery, Bootstrap, C, C#, Git Python

#### Languages

**English** 

Chinese

Korean

#### **Hobbies**

As a highly active and adventurous professional, my hobbies include outdoor activities such as hiking, sports, fitness and meditation. I have a keen interest in different cuisines from different ethnic groups and enjoy partaking in multicultural activities. I enjoy literature of both fiction and non-fiction natures and can often be found reading a book outdoors.

DamingGlass is a global trading company. The core business is the purchase, shipping, and sale of original glass sheets from China to Korea.

My responsibilities were:

- Established online stores from scratch based on WordPress and Cafe24 to enable customers to order products and track orders online, mainly using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, PHP.
- Design and amending product detail pages, model pictures, banners, thumbnails, ad posters.
- Managing product information on different e-commerce platforms, such as NaverShopping, Gmarket and 11 street stores.
- Management marketing based google ads and naver ads, and nested ads in above e-stores.
- Translating documents and contracts between Chinese and Korean.

#### Web Designer, Sappira, South Korea

JULY 2013 - APRIL 2015

Sappira is a company that designs, produces, and sells clothing for medical and entertainment companies in Korea.

My responsibilities were:

- Maintained product content across different online store platforms,
- Design and amending product detail pages, model pictures, banners, thumbnails, ad posters.
- Creating and maintaining user pages, mainly using HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Promote products through Korean actors, Instagram bloggers and Facebook ads.

### Education

#### React Development, General Assambly, Melbourne

MAY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

#### Bachelor of Information Technology, Deakin University, Melbourne

MARCH 2018 - NOVEMBER 2020

**Obtained Average Distinction** 

Majors: Application Development

Graduate Certificate of Business Analytics, Kaplan Business School Australia, Melbourne

JULY 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Majors: Business Analytics